Now let's talk about the brokerage report.
Gaurav has joined us with a full report.
Gaurav, good morning.
Tell me, first of all let's talk about the
telecom sector where IFL has
increased the target price on many companies. So,
if we
suggest to vodafoneidea.com that investors should
invest and going forward,
due to the improvement in the financials of Vodafone-Idea, we can
also see a positive impact on Indust Towers
and Indust Towers can
also reinstate dividends in the future. And
finally, they believe that somewhere
they are seeing two rounds of
tariff hike, which means they are expecting it. And due to this,
somewhere they have
done this for Vodafone-Idea and Bharti because they believe that
in the last few years, we have seen
that the
firm rating has remained intact but the target price has been
cut to ₹2500000.
Finally, let's talk about ICICI Loyd.
As the results have come, a very
good quarter for ICICI.  Lord had
reported that the growth has been quite good.
They have also reduced their combined ratio
estimator for exit ratio to
101.5. Due to this,
if we talk about brokerages, for example,
HSBC has maintained a hold/buy rating
and has set a target price of ₹10
because they believe that
if we talk about positives, then market share gain,
strong premium growth, all these have been
positives
in this quarter and going forward, these
comments on market share and combined ratio will
remain very positive for the company.
Due to this, Evek has also maintained a buy rating and set a
target price of ₹10.
If we talk about Macquarie,
there they have maintained an underperform rating and
we saw improvement in the target price of ₹1000000.
But if we talk about valuations, for
now, this stock is  It
trades at a 6.1 times price to book ratio,
which is slightly above the range according to Macquarie
and that is why they have maintained an
underperform rating. So
going forward, it will be very important to keep an eye on these companies
because
we are seeing a very strong view from the brokerage Jas.
Thank you very much Gaurav
for giving this complete update.